brokenbulbstudios.com 2016-12-08

# Privacy Policy | Broken Bulb Game Studios

## Pushing The Limits of Fun  
One Game at a Time

The following sets forth Broken Bulb Studios Privacy Policy pertaining to all players whom access any of our games (the ‘Services’).  Please note that this Privacy Policy is limited to the information collected and used by Broken Bulb Studios through use of any of our Services.  By using our Services, you agree that Broken Bulb Studios has the right to access and maintain the information as set out below.

It is advised that you review this Policy regularly as it may be amended from time to time, without notice. If you would like to be notified of any changes, please contact [privacy@brokenbulbstudios.com](mailto:privacy@brokenbulbstudios.com) and we will e-mail to inform you of any updates.

**What We Collect**

To use our Services, you must log in using your Facebook username and password.  We do not store or collect this information.  We utilize Facebook’s API to grant you access to the game.  The Facebook API provides an authentication protocol that allows users to approve the application to act on their behalf without sharing their password.

Broken Bulb Studios only collects the minimal amount of information required to deliver the intended game experience. This information is provided to us by Facebook with your prior authorization.  Please consult their privacy policy for more information.

Our Services also collects non-personal data through the use of server-based ‘session variables’, which we use to achieve important site functionality.  Our Services records IP addresses from all users.  An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the internet.  We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, to analyze trends, to track user movement, and to gather broad demographic information, all for the purpose of continually improving our Services.  IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information, and their collection is standard procedure in most web-server environments.

Broken Bulb Studios may ask you for your email address, to allow us to contact you with information on our Services.  You are not obliged to share this information. Please note that any email address provided will be used for our records only, and will not be given to any third party.

Broken Bulb Studios will never at any time ask you for your credit card or bank account information, your Facebook login or password, or national identification numbers via any unsolicited means, including email and telephone calls.

**Cookies**

When you access our Services, ‘cookies’  will automatically be sent to your computer.  A ‘cookie’  is a small text file recorded on your hard drive that identifies you as a unique user and contains certain information about your particular login session and/or use of our Services.  Broken Bulb Studios uses this to improve the quality of our Services, make recommendations, and make the Services easier to use.

**Deleting Information**

Our Services can be accessed through Facebook only.  You can change or delete any personal information by changing the applicable information found in your Facebook account. However, by deleting the entirety of this information your account may become deactivated.

**Children Under The Age of 13**

Broken Bulb Studios does not knowingly collect nor solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allows such persons to access our Services.  If you are 13 years old or younger, please do not attempt to use our Services, or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address.  In the event that Broken Bulb Studios learns that this information has been provided, it will be deleted as quickly as possible.

**Third Party Links**

Broken Bulb Studios’ Services may include third party links as a way to purchase or offer virtual, in-game currency (“Virtual Currency”) as well as virtual, in-game goods (“Virtual Goods”) by using legal tender.  These other sites maintain their own policies regarding the collection and use of personal information.  Please note that it is up to you to review these policies.

Broken Bulb Studios will have no access to any information you provide to these third parties.

**Contact Information**

For any queries regarding this Policy, please contact [privacy@brokenbulbstudios.com](mailto:privacy@brokenbulbstudios.com).
